https://musclecarclub.com/privacy-policy/

Terms and Conditions
Legal Restrictions and Terms and Conditions for Use of Web Site
TRADEMARK NOTICE:
The contents of this web site are owned by Musclecarclub.com and thus are protected from copying and simulation under national and international laws. Any and all text, graphics, and the general appearance of this web site are not to be reproduced or copied without the express written permission of Musclecarclub.com.
GENERAL NOTICE:
Musclecarclub.com strives to ensure that the information contained in this web site is accurate and reliable. However, Musclecarclub.com and the World Wide Web (or Web Site Host) are not infallible and errors may sometimes occur. Therefore, to the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, Musclecarclub.com disclaims any warranty of any kind, whether express or implied, as to any matter whatsoever relating to this web site, including without limitation the merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose. Musclecarclub.com will not be liable or responsible for any damages or injuries caused by use of this web site (such as viruses, omissions or misstatements). Musclecarclub.com may from time to time revise the information, services and the resources contained in this web site and reserves the right to make such changes without any obligation to notify past, current or prospective visitors. In no event shall Musclecarclub.com be liable for any indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising out of any use of the information contained herein.
HYPER-LINKS NOTICE:
The web site may link to sites not maintained or related to Musclecarclub.com. Hyper-text links are provided as a service to users and are not sponsored by or affiliated with this web site or Musclecarclub.com. Musclecarclub.com has not reviewed any or all of the sites hyper-linked to or from this web site and is not responsible for the content of any other sites. The links are to be accessed at the user’s own risk, and Musclecarclub.com makes no representations or warranties about the content, completeness, or accuracy of these links or the sites hyper-linked to this web site. Further, Musclecarclub.com does not implicitly endorse third-party sites hyper-linked to this web site.
COPYRIGHT NOTICE:
The graphic images, buttons, graphic layout, and text contained in this web site are the exclusive property of Musclecarclub.com and, except for personal use, may not be copied, distributed, or displayed, or reproduced or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without the prior written permission of Musclecarclub.com.
NON-ORIGINAL CONTENT:
In some instances, Musclecarclub.com has incorporated non-original content such as text or pictures, in this website. Proper credit has been given when the owner is known. In many cases, the original owner is not known, and thus Musclecarclub.com is unable to give the proper credit for the subject material. If you are the legal owner of such material, and wish to have it credited to you or removed from the website, please contact the webmaster and the appropriate changes will be made in a reasonable amount of time.
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Aquasource Faucet has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting Aquasource Faucet, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to third party Websites
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of this website then feel free to use our contact page.
